<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Programming Polyglot</title>
    <link>https://yulia-samoilovich.github.io/blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Programming Polyglot</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.126.1</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 13:00:38 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://yulia-samoilovich.github.io/blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing E-Commerce Customer Behaviour and Churn</title>
      <link>https://yulia-samoilovich.github.io/blog/posts/ecommerce-churn-prediction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 13:00:38 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://yulia-samoilovich.github.io/blog/posts/ecommerce-churn-prediction/</guid>
      <description>In this post, I explore and analyze some e-commerce customer data by identifying patterns in customer satisfaction and churn.
The dataset used for this analysis includes information on customer demographics, purchasing behavior, and satisfaction scores. Key features include:
CustomerID Unique identifier for each customer. Gender
Gender of the customer (Male/Female). MaritalStatus
Marital status of the customer (Married/Single/Divorced). PreferedOrderCat Preferred order category of the customer (e.g., Fashion, Grocery, Mobile). SatisfactionScore Satisfaction score given by the customer (1 to 5).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT vs Claude: Ambiguity Resolution (Part I)</title>
      <link>https://yulia-samoilovich.github.io/blog/posts/syntactic-ambiguity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 12:12:38 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://yulia-samoilovich.github.io/blog/posts/syntactic-ambiguity/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;One morning I shot an elephant in my pajamas.&amp;rdquo; - Groucho Marx Syntactic ambiguities occur when a sentence can have multiple meanings. For example, consider the sentence from the famous Groucho Marx joke above. This sentence is ambiguous because it&amp;rsquo;s unclear whether the elephant was in pajamas or Groucho Marx was in pajamas while shooting the elephant. If you&amp;rsquo;re curious which interpretation Groucho Marx meant, here is the full quote: &amp;ldquo;One morning I shot an elephant in my pajamas.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
